

I am actively looking for job change in Asp.net MVC, entity framework, Angular 4, Asp. net webapi, ADO. NET, Sql server, Oracle, Mysql.



Current Designation: Associate Total Experience: 5 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Notice Period: 1 Month Current Company: Cognizant Technology Solutions India Ltd

Current Location: Pune Highest Degree: MCA [Computers]

Pref. Location: Pune

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: ASP.Net MVC, WebAPI, SQL Server, Entity Framework, OOPS, C#, Angular JS, ASP.NET Web forms, MYSQL,

Oracle, LINQ, . Net, DOT NET

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 19-Jan-21 Last Modified: 19-Jan-21

### **Summary**

5 Years of experience as Application Developer in software design, development, implementation of web and client server applications using Microsoft Technologies.

Hands on application development using C#, Web Form inASP.NET using C#, as the code-behind language, ADO.NET Experience in developing application using Multi-tier architecture.

Knowledge in working with MVC 5, linq, Entity Framework.

Knowledge in working with WebApi, Angular 2+.

Experience in writing Stored Procedures using MS SQL Server 2016, MYSQL 5.5.

Ability to learn & develop using new technologies quickly.

Excellent communication and interpersonal skills.

Experience in working with GIT.

# Work Experience

#### Cognizant Technology Solutions India Ltd as Associate

Dec 2020 to Till Date

I am currently working in BFSI domain.

#### Sagitec Solutions as Software Engineer

Jan 2018 to Dec 2020

Client : Unemployment Insurance

: Software Engineer Role

Technical Environment :ASP.NET 4.5, C#,Entity Framework,Sql SERVER 2017, Visual Studio 2015,MVC 5

Description : Unemployment Insurance is fully integrated browser based application provides weekly wages to

unemployed people.

#### Soham Consultants as Application Developer

Jan 2016 to Dec 2017

I was workin as Trainee Application Developer and my job was in development

### **Education**

UG: BCA (Computers) from SGBAU University, Amravati. in 2013

PG: MCA (Computers) from SGBAU University, Amravati. in 2016

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

National Service Scheme Certificate

#### IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
ASP.Net MVC	5	2020	2 Year(s)
ADO.NET , MS SQLServer	2013	2020	5 Year(s)
WEBAPI		2020	
Entity Framework		2020	

# **Languages Known**

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Proficient			
Hindi	Proficient			
Marathi	Proficient			

### **Affirmative Action**

Physically Challenged: No

## **Work Authorization**

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time